{"data":[{"question":"What is she so nervous ________?","a":"about","b":"for","c":"to","d":"with","answer":"1","explain":"\n- To be nervous about sth: worried or frightened about something, and unable to relax.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"Such ________ statements are likely to provoke strong opposition.","a":"tend","b":"tendency","c":"tendentious","d":"tendentiously","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Such + Noun\/noun phrase: of the same kind as the thing or person which has already been mentioned.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"The man was found guilty ________ from his employer.","a":"of stealing","b":"for stealing","c":"in stealing","d":"with stealing","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Be\/Find guilty of sth\/doing sth: responsible for behaviour that is morally or socially unacceptable.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"She went on her work with an air of ________.","a":"determinant","b":"determination","c":"determine","d":"determined","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Preposition (by, of, in, on...) + Verb_ing\/noun\/noun phrase (adj + noun).\u00a0\n- Determination: the quality of trying to do something even when it is difficult.\u00a0\n- Determinant: something that strongly influences what you do or how you behave.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"He ________ that if we started at dawn, we would be there by noon.","a":"reason","b":"reasoned","c":"reasonable","d":"reasonably","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"The patient is getting on ________.","a":"satisfied","b":"satisfaction","c":"satisfactory","d":"satisfactorily","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Adverbs often go after verbs that they modify","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"My brother and my sister ________ engineers.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"has","d":"have","answer":"2","explain":"\n- My brother and my sister + plural verb","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"He did not look at straight to his father's eyes. He answered ________.","a":"fearful","b":"fearfully","c":"fearless","d":"fearlessly","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Adverbs go after verbs that they modify","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"The earth, ________ is the fifth largest planet in the solar system, is the third planet from the sun.","a":"who","b":"whom","c":"which","d":"that","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Which: used as the subject in the non-defining relative clause\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"They took part in school's activities ________.","a":"keen","b":"keenly","c":"keenness","d":"keener","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Adverbs go after verbs that they modify","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"}]}